Guide to the Western Teleplays Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Western Teleplays Collection
1958-1982
WA MSS S-1593
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
8
(16 boxes)
Collection contains 193 scripts for three popular network television shows: Bat Masterson, Gunsmoke, and Little House on the Prairie. There are 138 Bat Masterson scripts, 17 Gunsmoke scripts, and 38 Little House on the Prairie scripts. Many of the scripts have been heavily annotated; more than a dozen of the Bat Masterson episodes are represented by multiple drafts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ongoing collection of documents acquired by gift and purchase from various sources. The first accession, making up Series I, II, and III were purchased from Walter Reuben in 1987 and 1988. Second accession of interfiled Bat Masterson filmscripts were pruchased from Walter Reuben in 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The Western Teleplays Collection contains 193 scripts for three popular network television shows: Bat Masterson, Gunsmoke, and Little House on the Prairie. The scripts have been organized into series by show.
Series I, Bat Masterson contains 138 scripts from 1958-1961. They have been organized by episode number which ranges from 1B through 107B. More than a dozen episodes are represented by multiple drafts, but there are no scripts present for episodes 35B, 72B, 74B or 95B. The scripts for nearly every episode contain revised pages (which typically include the date of their revision), and many of the scripts are heavily annotated "cutting scripts" which reflect the final editing of the episode before it was broadcast.
Series II, Gunsmoke, consists of seventeen scripts from 1966-1975. The bulk of the scripts are dated between July 1973 and February 1975. As the Gunsmoke scripts do not include an episode number, they have been organized by date of last noted revision.
Series III, Little House on the Prairie, contains scripts for thirty-eight episodes from 1974-1982. The first thirty-three scripts are arranged by episode numbers. The earliest numbered episode is #3 which is dated July 8, 1974. The bulk of the series falls between episode #59 (April 30, 1976) and episode #200 (January 7, 1982). Five unnumbered and undated scripts for Little House on the Prairie episodes are arranged alphabetically by title after the numbered episodes.
The box and folder list which follows includes the title of each episode (including earlier versions where so indicated on the script), the date of the final noted revisions for each script, the kind of script represented (e.g. draft, revised draft, cutting, etc.), and the names of any writers, directors, and producers that were identified in the script.
Bat Masterson (Television program); Gunsmoke (Television program); Little house on the prairie (Television program); Western television programs; Television scripts
- Bat Masterson, 1958 Feb 22; Series I
  - 1B. Showdown, 1958 Feb 22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Story by Andy White Frank Pittman. Teleplay by Gene Levitt.
  - 2B. Stampede at Tent City, 1958 Jul 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Morton Fine; David Friedkin.
  - 3B. Two Graves for Swan Valley, 1958 Jul 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Story by Andy White, Frank Pittman. Teleplay by Andy White. Directed by Walter Donigan.
  - 4B-Rev. Man of Action, 1959 Jan 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Teleplay by Gene Levitt.
  - 5B. A Noose Fits Anybody, 1958 Aug 8 (Box 1, Folder 4a)
    Teleplay by John Elliotte.
  - 5B. A Noose Fits Anybody, 1958 Aug 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by John Elliotte.
  - 6B. Trail Pirate, 1958 Aug 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Wells Root.
  - 7B. Cattle Drive, 1958 Aug 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 7B. Cattle Drive (Revised version), 1958 Aug 20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 8B. Buffalo Kill, 1958 Sep 18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Leo Gorman.
  - 9B. Sherman's March Through Dodge City, 1958 Sep 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Teleplay by Maurice Tombragel.
  - 10B. Bear Bait!, 1958 Sep 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Andy White.
  - 11B. The Fighter, 1958 Aug 8 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    First draft, second revision. Teleplay by Turnley Walker.
  - 11B. The Fighter (Revised version), 1958 Sep 10 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Turnley Walker.
  - 12B. Dude's Folly, 1958 Sep 24 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Don Brinkley.
  - 13B. The Phantom Ship, 1958 Sep 26 (Box 2, Folder 14a)
    Teleplay by Wells Root.
  - 13B. The Desert Ship, 1958 Sep 30 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Cutting script.
  - 14B. Election Day, 1958 Oct 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Teleplay by Turnley Walker.
  - 14B. Election Day (Revised version), 1958 Oct 6 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 15B-Rev. Sharpshooter, 1958 Nov 25 (Box 2, Folder 17a)
  - 15B-Rev. Sharpshooter, 1958 Dec 4 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Maurice Tombragel. Directed by John Rich.
  - 16B. Cheyenne Club, 1958 Oct 14 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Teleplay by D.D. Beauchamp.
  - 17B. Double Trouble in Trinidad, 1958 Oct 23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Story by Richard O'Connor. Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 18B. The Treasure of Worry Hill, 1958 Oct 17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Gene Levitt.
  - 19B. One Bullet from Broken Bow, 1958 Nov 3 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Andy White. Produced by Frank Pittman; Andy White. Directed by Allen Miner.
  - 20B. License to Cheat, 1958 Nov 25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Teleplay by George F. Slavin.
  - 20B. License to Cheat (Revised version), 1958 Dec 5 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Draft script. Teleplay by George F. Slavin.
  - 21B. River Boat, 1958 Nov 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 22B. A Personal Matter, 1958 Nov 20 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Cutting script. Teleplay by Fran van Hartesveldt.
  - 23B. Marked Deck, 1958 Nov 26 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Draft script. Story by Charles Smith. Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 23B. Marked Deck (Revised version), 1958 Dec 2 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Story by Charles Smith. Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 24B. Battle of the Pass, 1958 Dec 15 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Editing script. Teleplay by Don Brinkley.
  - 25B. Incident at Leadville, 1958 Jan 10 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Sixth revision. Teleplay by Harry Essex.
  - 26B. The Tumbleweed Wagon, 1958 Dec 22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    First draft. Teleplay by Wells Root.
  - 26B. The Tumbleweed Wagon (Revised version), 1959 Jan 12 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 27B. Blondes Can Be Tamed, 1958 Dec 9 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    First draft. Teleplay by John Elliotte.
  - 27B. Blondes Can Be Tamed (Revised version), 1959 Jan 20 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Fifth revision. Teleplay by John Elliotte.
  - 28B. Deadline, 1959 Jan 28 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Editing draft. Teleplay by George F. Slavin. Produced by Frank Pittman; Andy White. Directed by John Rich.
  - 29B. The Death of Bat Masterson, 1959 Feb 27 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Draft. Teleplay by Don Brinkley. Directed by Allen Crosland.
  - 30B. Follow the Gleam, 1959 Jan 28 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    First draft and revisions. Teleplay by Wells Root.
  - 30B. A Matter of Honor (Revision of Follow the Gleam), 1959 Feb 9 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Draft. Teleplay by Wells Root. Produced by Frank Pittman, Andy WHite. Directed by Walter Doniger.
  - 31B. Lottery of Death, 1959 Feb 17 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Editing draft. Teleplay by Don Ingalls.
  - 32B. The Black Pearls, 1959 Apr 3 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Draft. Teleplay by Wells Root. Directed by Crosland.
  - 33B. The Romany Knives, 1959 Mar 13 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Teleplay by Barney Slater.
  - 34B. Promised Land, 1959 Mar 27 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Fifth revision. Teleplay by D.D. Beauchamp.
  - 36B-Rev. The Conspiracy, Part I, 1959 Apr 21 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Teleplay by Don Brinkley.
  - 37B. The Conspiracy, Part II, 1959 Apr 21 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 38B. Wanted - Dead, 1959 May 8 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Eighth revision, cutting. Teleplay by Gene Levitt.
  - 39B-Rev. Shakedown at St. Joe, 1959 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Draft. Teleplay by Maurice Tombragel.
  - 39B-Rev. Shakedown at St. Joe (Revised version), 1959 Jun 11 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 40B. The Canvas and the Cane, 1959 Jul 21 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 41B. To the Manner Born, 1959 May 29 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 41B. To the Manner Born (Revised version), 1959 Jul 14 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 42B. Lady Luck, 1959 Aug 3 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Teleplay by Harry Essex.
  - 43B. Death and Taxes, 1959 Jun 15 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Teleplay by Paul Franklin.
  - 43B. Death and Taxes (Revised version), 1959 Aug 3 (Box 4, Folder 52a)
  - 43B. Death and Taxes (Revised version), 1959 Aug 6 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 44B. No Funeral for Thorn (Revision of Luke Short's Long Shot), 1959 Jul 27 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Teleplay by John McGreevey.
  - 45B. The Barbary Castle, 1959 Jul 13 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 45B. The Barbary Castle (Revised version), 1959 Aug 24 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 46B. Come Out Fighting, 1959 Sep 28 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 47B. The Inner Circle, 1959 Jul 31 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Teleplay by Andy White.
  - 47B. The Inner Circle (Revised version), 1959 Aug 12 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 48B. Garrison Finish, 1959 Aug 6 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - 48B. Garrison Finish (Revised version), 1959 Oct 19 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Maurice Tombragel.
  - 49B. Dead Men Don't Pay Debts, 1959 Aug 6 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    Teleplay by Dan Ullman.
  - 49B. Dead Men Don't Pay Debts (Revised Version), 1959 Aug 25 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - 50B. Gold Is Where You Steal It, 1959 Sep 11 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    Teleplay by Michael Fessier.
  - 51B. Who'll Buy My Violence?, 1959 Sep 10 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Don Brinkley.
  - 52B. The Pied Piper of Dodge City, 1959 Oct 26 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Barney Slater.
  - 53B-Rev. Blood on the Money, 1960 Apr 12 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 54B. The Elusive Baguette, 1959 Oct 7 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - 54B. The Elusive Baguette (Revised version), 1960 Feb 25 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - 54B. The Elusive Baguette (Revised version), 1960 Mar 28 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    Eleventh revision. Teleplay by George F. Slavin.
  - 55B. Bat Plays A Dead Man's Hand, 1959 Oct 6 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Harry Essex.
  - 56B. Flume to the Mother Lode, 1959 Nov 3 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Gene Levitt.
  - 57B. The Million Dollar Photograph, 1959 Oct 14 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    Teleplay by Samuel A. Peeples.
  - 57B. A Picture of Death (Revision of The Million Dollar Photograph), 1959 Oct 22 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - 58B. Death by the Half Dozen, 1959 Nov 17 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Guy de Vry.
  - 59B. Six Feet of Gold, 1959 Oct 29 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - 59B. Six Feet of Gold (Revised version), 1959 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - 60B. Deadly Diamonds, 1959 Dec 4 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by John McGreevey.
  - 61B. Pigeon and Hawk, 1959 Nov 25 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    Editing draft. Teleplay by John Tucker Battle.
  - 62B. The Disappearance of Bat Masterson, 1960 Jan 21 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - 63B. Cattle and Canes, 1960 Jan 7 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - 64B. Mr. Fourpaws, 1959 Dec 30 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    Teleplay by D. D. Beauchamp; Mary M. Beauchamp. Produced by Pittman & White. Directed by Eddie Davis.
  - 65B. The Snare, 1960 Jan 25 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - 66B. Stage to Nowhere, 1960 Feb 11 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Wells Root; Ron Bishop.
  - 67B. Three Bullets for Bat, 1960 Feb 1 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Dean Riesner. Directed by Crosland.
  - 68B. Incident at Fort Bowie, 1960 Feb 16 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - 69B. The Reluctant Witness, 1960 Feb 8 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by George Slavin.
  - 70B. Go For Broke, 1960 Feb 23 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    Editing draft. Teleplay by Paul Franklin.
  - 71B. No Way Out, 1960 Feb 29 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - 73B. Wanted - Alive, Please!, 1960 Mar 17 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    Teleplay by D.D. Beauchamp; Mary M. Beauchamp.
  - 75B. High Card Loses (Revision of Mail Order Dynamite), 1960 Sep 12 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - 76B. Bat Trap (Revision of Turkey Shoot), 1960 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by John Tucker Battle.
  - 77B-Rev. Last Stop to Austin, 1960 Oct 19 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    Teleplay by Teddi Sherman.
  - 78B. Law of the Land, 1960 Jul 2 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Andy White.
  - 79B. Farmer with a Badge, 1960 Jun 28 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Alan Woods, Monroe Manning.
  - 80B. Death by Decree, 1960 Sep 23 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - 81B. The Lady Plays Her Hand, 1960 Aug 4 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    (Revision of The Seventeenth Hand)
  - 82B. Hang the Man High, 1960 Sep 12 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - 82B-Rev. Jeopardy at Jackson Hole, 1961 Feb 9 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    Teleplay by Guy de Vry.
  - 83B. Debt of Honor, 1960 Aug 18 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    Seventh revision. Teleplay by Barney Slater.
  - 84B. The Rage of Princess Anne, 1961 Feb 9 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Ellis Kadison.
  - 85B. The Hunter, 1960 Sep 15 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Joe Stone, Paul King.
  - 86B. Murder Can Be Dangerous, 1960 Sep 29 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    Fifth revision. Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 87B. The Fatal Garment, 1960 Sep 8 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    Teleplay by S.H. Barnett; Fran Van Hartesveldt.
  - 87B. The Fatal Garment (Revised version), 1960 Oct 3 (Box 8, Folder 104a)
  - 87B. The Fatal Garment (Revised version), 1960 Nov 8 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    Fifth revision. Teleplay by S.H. Barnett; Fran Van Hartesveldt.
  - 87B. The Fatal Garment (Revised version), 1960 Nov 9 (Box 8, Folder 105a)
    Sixth revision. Teleplay by S.H. Barnett; Fran Van Hartesveldt.
  - 87B. The Fatal Garment (Revised (Box 8, Folder 105b)
    - version), 1960 Nov 14
    - Seventh revision. Teleplay by S.H. Barnett; Fran Van Hartesveldt.
  - 88B. Tempest at Tioga Pass (Revised version), 1960 Sep 8 (Box 8, Folder 105c)
  - 88B. Tempest at Tioga Pass, 1960 Nov 22 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - 89B. Dakota Showdown (Revision of The Lethel Sex), 1960 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 106a)
  - 89B. Dakota Showdown (Revision of The Lethal Sex), 1960 Oct 6 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - 90B. Last of the Night Riders, 1960 Oct 13 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    (Revision of End of the Doolins)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Richard Collins.
  - 91B. End of the Line (Revised version), 1960 Oct 20 (Box 9, Folder 108a)
    Teleplay by Lee Karson.
  - 91B. End of the Line (Revised version), 1960 Oct 26 (Box 9, Folder 108b)
  - 91B. End of the Line (Revised version), 1960 Nov 1 (Box 9, Folder 108c)
  - 91B. End of the Line, 1960 Nov 5 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    Editing draft. Teleplay by Lee Karson.
  - 92B. A Time to Die, 1960 Oct 25 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Frank Granville.
  - 93B. Ledger of Guilt, 1961 Mar 2 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - 94B. The Price of Paradise, 1960 Nov 7 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - 96B. Dead Man's Claim, 1960 Dec 22 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by George F. Slavin.
  - 97B. The Court Martial of Major Mars, 1960 Dec 2 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    Teleplay by Joe Stone, Paul King. Directed by Elliott Lewis.
  - 98B. Bullwhacker's Bounty, 1960 Dec 1 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - 98B. Bullwhacker's Bounty (Revised version), 1960 Dec 6 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - 99B. The Fourth Man, 1961 Mar 22 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    Cutting draft. Teleplay by Mikhail Rykoff.
  - 100B. The Prescott Campaign, 1960 Dec 21 (Box 9a, Folder 118)
  - 101B. Run For Your Money, 1960 Dec 30 (Box 9a, Folder 119)
  - 102B. A Lesson in Violence, 1961 Jan 6 (Box 9a, Folder 120)
  - 103B. The Marble Slab (Revised version), 1961 Jan 10 (Box 9a, Folder 120a)
    Teleplay by Glenhall Taylor, Paul Franklin.
  - 103B. The Marble Slab, 1961 Jan 13 (Box 9a, Folder 121)
  - 104B. Terror on the Trinity, 1961 Jan 23 (Box 9a, Folder 122)
  - 105B. Episode in Eden, 1961 Jan 31 (Box 9a, Folder 123)
  - 106B. Meeting at Mimbers, 1961 Feb 1 (Box 9a, Folder 124)
    Teleplay by Ron Bishop.
  - 107B. Dagger Dance, 1961 Mar 9 (Box 9a, Folder 125)
- Gunsmoke, 1966 Jul 8; Series II
  - The Moonstone, 1966 Jul 8 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Paul Savage. Produced by John Mantley.
  - The Saga of Benjamin Brown, 1973 Jul 24 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Ray Goldrup. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - Luke Rumbaugh, 1973 Sep 12 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Paul Savage. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Comancheros of Cibola Blanca. Parts I & II, 1974 Feb 28 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Paul Savage. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Comancheros of Cibola Blanca. Parts I & II (Revised), 1974 Mar 18 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    Second revised final draft. Teleplay by Paul Savage. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - In Performance of Duty, 1974 Mar 6 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    Final draft. Teleplay by William Keys. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Colonel, 1974 Mar 8 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Arthur Dales. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Stringers, 1974 Apr 9 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Ron Bishop. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Fourth Victim, 1974 May 7 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Jim Byrnes. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Fourth Victim (Revised version), 1974 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Jim Byrnes. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - The Iron Men, 1974 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by John Mantley. Produced by Leonard Katzman.
  - Wilderness, 1974 Oct 11 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Jim Byrnes. Produced by John Stephens.
  - The Land, 1974 Oct 23 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    Revised final draft. Story by Herman Groves. Teleplay by Jim Byrnes. Produced by John G. Stephens.
  - The Busters, 1974 Nov 11 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    First draft. Teleplay by Jim Byrnes. Produced by John G. Stephens.
  - The Marryin' (No. 1), 1974 Nov 21 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Earl W. Wallace. Produced by John G. Stephens.
  - The Hallelujah Man, 1974 Dec 19 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    First draft. Teleplay by William Kelly. Directed by John G. Stephens.
  - The Devil's Bounty, 1975 Feb 3 (Box 11, Folder 142)
- Little House on the Prairie, 1974 Jul 8; Series III
  - 3. The 100 Mile Walk, 1974 Jul 8 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Ward Hawkins.
  - 59. Injun Kid, 1976 Apr 30 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Arthur Heinemann.
  - 71. To Live With Fear. Parts I & II, 1976 Jul 19 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    Final draft. Teleplay by B.W. Sandefur; John Hawkins.
  - 72. The Wisdom of Solomon, 1976 Dec 13 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Scott Swanton.
  - 76. The Election, 1976 Dec 8 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    Second draft. Teleplay by B.W. Sandefor.
  - 90. The High Cost of Being Right, 1977 Jun 14 (Box 12, Folder 148)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Don Balluck.
  - 93. I'll Be Waving as You Drive Away (Part I), 1978 Jan 18 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Carole Raschella; Michael Raschella. Produced by William Claxton.
  - 94. I'll Be Waving as You Drive Away. Part II, 1978 Jan 16 (Box 12, Folder 150)
    Second draft. Teleplay by Carole Raschella; Michael Raschella.
  - 94. I'll Be Waving as You Drive Away. Part II (Revised), 1978 Feb 1 (Box 12, Folder 151)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Carole Raschella; Michael Raschella.
  - 102. Be My Friend, 1977 Nov 7 (Box 12, Folder 152)
    First draft. Teleplay by Michael Landon. Produced by John Hawkins. Directed by Michael Landon.
  - 107. Men Will Be Boys, 1978 Apr 27 (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - 110. As Long As We're Together, 1978 May 1 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    First draft. Teleplay by Michael Landon.
  - 112. The Godsister, 1978 Jun 6 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - 115. There's No Place Like Home. Part I, 1978 Apr 19 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    First Draft. Teleplay by Michael Landon.
  - 116. There's No Place Like Home. Part II, 1978 Jun 5 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - 117. The Man Inside, 1978 May 9 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - 120. Blind Journey. Part I, 1978 Jul 18 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    First draft. Teleplay by John T. Dugan.
  - 120. Blind Journey. Part I (Revised version), 1978 Aug 10 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    Final Draft. Teleplay by John T. Dugan.
  - 122. Dance With Me, 1978 Oct 3 (Box 13, Folder 161)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Paul Wolff.
  - 125. The Sound of Children, 1978 Oct 16 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - 142. The King Is Dead, 1979 Mar 12 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Michael Landon.
  - 147. Crossed Connections, 1978 Jun 27 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - 160. Dark Sage, 1981 Jul 27 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Vince R. Gutierrez.
  - 164. No Beast So Fierce, 1980 Jun 24 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - 164. No Beast So Fierce (Revised version), 1981 Jul 21 (Box 14, Folder 167)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Carole Raschella; Michael Raschella.
  - 176. The Legacy, 1981 Nov 20 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - 177. To See the Light, 1980 Jun 30 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - 179. The Wave of the Future, 1981 Aug 3 (Box 14, Folder 170)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Jeri Taylor.
  - 185. The Lost Ones. Part II, 1981 Jan 23 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - 192. The Reincarnation of Nellie (Part One) (Box 15, Folder 172)
    Draft. Teleplay by Michael Landon.
  - 193. The Reincarnation of Nellie. Part II (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - 197. Stone Soup, 1981 Nov 18 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    Revised final draft. Teleplay by Peter Dixon.
  - 200. Days of Sunshine, Days of Shadow. Part II, 1982 Jan 7 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    Final draft. Teleplay by Chris Abbott.
  - Blizzard (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Halloween Story (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Journey in the Spring (Box 15, Folder 178)
    Draft.
  - The Music Box (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Quarantine (Box 15, Folder 180)